linkdir.co.uk 2018-10-17

# Privacy Policy | Link Directory

Please read carefully the Privacy Policy below and the _Terms of Use_ before you use LinkDir.co.uk, use our tools and before conducting any type of transaction with LinkDir.co.uk. By viewing and accessing LinkDir.co.uk, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by the _Terms of Use_.

**Data Collection**

LinkDir.co.uk does not save or collect any data of User unless User decides to register. However, f User decides to register LinkDir.co.uk, some personal data such as e-mail address will be required for registration. We do not save any kind of information which is not asked User directly in forms.

**Data Protection**

LinkDir.co.uk does not sell or share any kind of data for any kind of purpose to 3rd parties. We do not share your personal information to anyone. LinkDir.co.uk takes measures for data and code security. We implemented cryptographic functions in order to keep data safety.

**Cookies**

“Cookies” are data files that are sometimes downloaded to your personal computer upon visiting web sites on web. LinkDir.co.uk does not use cookies and will not access your personal computer in any way other than displaying on your browser.

**Minors**

LinkDir.co.uk tools are not targeted at minors, and minors may not register for any kind of services provided by LinkDir.co.uk.

**Seo And Website Analyses**

LinkDir.co.uk provides online monitoring and analysing web tools, including, but not limited to, the free Seo Tools and Website Tools. These tools requires domain names from user and as user proceed the form, LinkDir.co.uk will collect public data of given domain name and store it. The public information such as site title, description, homepage screenshot, most searched queries, domain age, etc. of domains will also be visible to other users. Whenever user types a domain, LinkDir.co.uk automatically start collecting public information of given domain.
